In this Lab, you will get to employ a very useful pattern.
このラボではとても役立つパターンを使います
You will use BigQuery to calculate useful aggregates,
BigQueryを使って役立つ計算を行います
percentile values, and the like over 70 million rows.
7千万を超える行の集計や パーセンタイル値などです
The result will go into a Pandas DataFrame of a dozen rows.
結果はPandas DataFrameの 多数の行に入力されます
You can then happily use that in-memory Pandas DataFrame for visualization.
そして そのインメモリPandas DataFrameを 可視化のために使用できます
So, this is the kind of thing that would take you hours if you did it any other way.
もし この作業を他の方法で行うなら 何時間もかかるでしょう
However, in the Lab,
でも このラボでは
you will create the graphs in seconds.
数秒でグラフを作成します
It's important to get this kind of interactive development workflow done.
こうした対話式の開発ワークフローを 定めることは重要です
Otherwise, you will not be able to work with large datasets easily.
これがないと 大量のデータセットで 簡単に作業できません
Well, you might think that you don't have to work with all of the data.
でも「すべてのデータを使う必要はない」 と考えるかもしれません
You can simply sample the dataset and work with a smaller sample.
単に小さなサンプルを抽出し それを処理すればよいのでは？
However, that is a bad practice in machine learning.
しかし これは機械学習では 不適切なプラクティスです
One thing I like to say is that
1つお伝えしたい点ですが
the key difference between statistics and machine learning,
統計学と機械学習には重要な違いがあります
is how we deal with outliers.
それは異常値の扱いです
In statistics, outliers tend to be removed.
統計学では 異常値をよく除外します
But in machine learning,
しかし機械学習では 通常
outliers tend to be learned.
異常値を学習します
And if you want to learn outliers,
異常値を学習したければ
you need to have enough examples of those outliers,
十分な数の異常値の実例が必要です
which essentially means that you have to work with all of your data.
つまり実質的に すべてのデータを使う必要があります
You have to have the distribution of outliers,
異常値や希少値がデータセット全体に
distributions of rare values throughout your dataset.
よく分散している必要があります
And in order to do that,
そのためには
you have to work with your complete dataset.
完全なデータセットを使うべきです
One way to do this,
その1つの方法を
is to do what you're going to do in this Lab,
このラボでお見せします
which is to use managed services like BigQuery,
それはBigQueryのようなマネージドサービスで
to process data at scale,
大規模にデータを処理することです
and then bring it back into more familiar in-memory structures like Pandas,
そしてPandasのような使い慣れた インメモリ構造にデータを戻し
and then use tools like the plotting libraries in Python.
Pythonのプロッティング ライブラリ などのツールを使います
So, this is a common working paradigm that we have to get familiar with.
これを実例として
And you will learn how to do this in the
この方法をラボで学習します